

Deepjyoti Dhar

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | DEVELOPER

Profile

Highly motivated person with expertise in graphic designing, social media management and development. I am very creative and can handle client needs effectively. I have over a year of experience working as a freelancer for artists, creators, and agencies as a designer.

Education

B.TECH(Mechanical Engg. UG)

Tezpur University (2021-25)

HS

Salt Brook Academy(2019-2021)

Skills

- Excellent graphic designing skills in PS. AI & Canva.
- Excellent skills in digital art
- Intermediate skills in copy writing
- Intermediate coder in C++, Java. JS.

Experience

DESIGNS

Designed Tshirts and Album arts

2021-2022

I was responsible for curating creative designs for the hostel and department tshirt for a few hostels in Tezpur University. Also collaborated with musical artist for their album art design.

- Hostel tshirt design for KWH & TMH.
- Made album art for various songs.

DEVELOPMENT

Developed my personal portfolio

2021-2022

Developed my own portfolio with an landing page an d also collaborated with some other developers on open source.

- Made the portfolio using HTML,CSS, JS, and react.
- Contributed in open source programs.

Contact

Phone +91 6901166191

E-mail deepjyoti26dhar@gmail.com

Address Sonari, Charaideo, ASSAM

LinkedIn click here